Sure.
Dense breast was covered by the red button
around here is the original message.
Modern highways and penetrated the dug.
Out on the right. So an accent works for
either side. Step in the way of the
abandoned road that just Langton it's like
passing through and closing the door
behind your. Obsolete trails run their big
crash brushstrokes break at right angles
for no reason. Only one leans to the log
and. The log in farm as the allure of
the cattle that everybody knows about
but if you have entered. It's only
access to the outside world is
a country road that dashes by some miles
north and next to the highway near the Red
River. Go red like the other farmers
here about the. Race is good after.
Signs so I'll ever. In the Valley. The
young people from miles around on the high
school. Boys graduate
a little older than those in the city
that's because they take time out for
a plan to help him with the harvest
they're out the. Girls don't come thirty
already players.
Are we going to play and they were for
not needed there were fine attention
discerning terms may be
aware I'm over now playing
a contentious event to try. Our best.
I can add half. Time and.
What are you doing to civilization.
The grown ups every year almost
a woman I'm out I'm
a man enough already. I wouldn't say that
oh what do you know about anything and
never got past
a nice grade. I'm to have plenty of
things they don't teach in school.
At an Indian candidate.
Pedophila I haven't had
time to formulate
a half. That they are ready. Yet.
I want. To talk
a lot. And I had already. OK
magazine. I. May
like to be going today about this ad.
Mash Meg back down to my advantage of.
Know i was there. I thought about
this thing Meg. And I so sure it's
a good thing we've been
a contender the way things were maybe an
upset it was pilot. But it be so much
easier for us and I
could come and have had
a panic attack. And I
think we've seen you in
a. Peon to be that going to have to.
Say the word. Never could get out.
Mike says good things about your
name. Everyone out of stock
a few might be gone too so Mr
Morgan. Now you must are getting
along our family don't make
a dollar. What you want to
see me about Mr Martin. You
know about my leg. Work.
My sister and I have got
a curious idea that it's hard to climb
a ladder without legs. But it is. I
thought I've got an idea that things are
getting
a little run down here. Can't do it much I
used to so they stopped me in the hiring
somebody. Help
a lot to be in charge I paid
thirty five cents an hour. To
make it for best it's all right now is
walk home after I went. And saw the last.
Paper at the center now
cut it back to the.
Sure it's all right with
the own name Oh yes.
I'm.
Trying to go if. I get help that he had
become too used to doing things alone.
I do hope
a good catch. Be
sure you don't want any more now Thanks
ma'am. But nobody will believe me when I
tell my operator. Was there. Well then
you know you're on methadone or known as
the mysterious Morgan. Highway. Well I won't
say any more now when I tell him what
a swell layout you've got here and that
you spread the best table in the valley
because this is self-protection here. We
seldom had any need to go to town. But
after they say about
a snake. Oh nothing. Except
things like Meg not being your daughter
or even related. Why don't they
have me. I guess I'd rather whisper
got up and find out the truth.
Fuck us oh. Well I say Meg mother and
father ran away and left
her when she was still
a baby. That's not true. About the
father went down south to find
a new from my life my going to die down
there and run away he denied us to make
legally not think the list about me. He was
only two years old when there's nothing
wrong with being adopted. Sure.
And the next time I hear anybody gossiping
about it I'll say so I've. Met in the
only adopted girl in the world.
Like I hate to run folks
but I think about it.
Kind of late so I started taking shortcuts
Rockhead would. You know your way
through those words. The wind. But I
take the long way around if I were you.
I run me out if it were three years I'm.
I was brave as the next man I was with.
What happened mate and I was
a kid there and you said you did not
accept words from a tree the tree in
a trail that drank no way I got. That I.
Got. That right because
I. Read it and I had
a way around that and I thank you and I
am
a bad. Mess but I got it and I. Thank
you. Thank you. Thank.
YOU THANK YOU. Thank you.
Thank you to.
Matt.
Rather. It's
a great lesson. I learned it wasn't
actually. Running against last.
Year's and I rather. Go to.
An add.
INS at. The
ash
mess.
As.
An F.
.
As.
Well as. S.
. Thank.
YOU THANK YOU
THANK.
YOU THANK YOU. Thank you Alan.
Thank.
YOU THANK.
You Yes Mr Starr may sleeping at night so
don't you worry about it. Hard work and
a big step in the right any bright. We're
going to make sure that we're glad to
have them. It's nice. That you know I've.
Been trying to. Make sure.
To be
a great help Bob. If
you happen to get out of here. Iran. You
scare the daylights out of last night.
Seems like the truth couldn't scare anybody
man aboard the truth you on your screen
was
a night almost we're not talking about. Now
don't tell me I imagined all that stuff
I went on knows what and I heard something
from things I don't know I don't know
whether it was
a scream you were talking about or just
the wind really well enough allows for
a. Part of Russia to judge
a practitioner you can
graduate school. And one of.
Them and. What kind of
a guy is paid anyway. The darn thing
wonderful small tiny tenement
from asbestos into the bottom of one of
a kind of trying to buy
from I. To die that way.
But what about that red
house. I remember hearing him
talk about it a long time
ago. But I've never had
a man to assume. You haven't. Been just
wanting me to put out of those words
since I was little. You know
anything about the scream.
I don't sound a man be
a friend. This
is what the markets are
working on that I myself.
Got
a story where were you last time but I
thought I said I would be working. Alone
to have
a camera guy even on shore money to
mortgage without you throwing up said not
a thanks are nice.
But you're not bowled over by the
rest of this I didn't write this off
a. Bus from the past coming in
asking for things I haven't got.
One of your posts or no I don't agree it's
my style. At the time and I doubt I need
to get married after you out of school and
on your own graduation just around the
corner. Why don't you two go ahead and get
married while you're still young enough
to enjoy. Talking to your mother that way
are you given enough your life to make
you go down to town and tell Don you're
ready any time either. He's being
transferred NORTH Well that settles Perry's
been courting you and I was in grammar
school if you don't marry him now you'll
meet some chick up north and then you'll
be
a dead duck. I'm going to change
every letter from Oregon. How do you
like it up there oh it's OK. I mean well
a couple things got me wondering. People
are going whose leg is that out of place
and how it works so back
in time ago you were still
a baby Dr Byrne first case
in the back. Amputated
a leg on the market kitchen table order
for someone my age at. The first time Dr
Byrne had a mass market.
Everybody knows it's not
a matter of there nothing
ever came of it do I still
a bachelor I don't know how I still
act like they love each other
a few times I've seen the me that he chose
a devoted latter brother Peter
I guess. The bride to be
a shame if you don't marry down
and go north with. By him I'm
a visa for you until they get
their search for me sometimes
a moron know about women the less I
know about women guy needs more than
a high school education to find out what
they're going to do next. And if you say
to them are going to get Impact Now I'm
going to go short bus route to work by
daylight on the way back here tonight but
if you can change your mind you can I go
downtown and there we don't. Do more
than talk things over you come back your
bride. You don't want dead
ducks my family do it. By.
Man.
Man. I feel like.
We are attacked by an.
American. I guess
makes Estrada question some press coverage
right now going to quite some time
trying to back out on his rhetoric
but I. Was going to. Write
a note and I think Robert you.
Allow yourself to question makers.
Because of him. Naming. The men he was
comparing. I think you were
asked to help the gas.
Out of
a sudden you're seeing grown ups. I
guess I don't like to see it happen. To
wish you were
a child again. I wish you
needed me just you depend. On
how much you're
a pretty girl always. You mean
everything around me. And to be
happy.
Late today. I had to go home first came
here through act at work. Here that would
be the quickest. Day
times. Or any other time.
Don't put so high
a price on courage that separated. The
lower status got more courage and manners.
Which are snapping turtle with a stake
in a crab at it with its teeth got
a share of. The beast
a long letter. We humans
were made that way.
We were born helpless but we don't have to
stay that way nobody's going to Carmel.
Who has nobody yet. Another is going to.
My preference.
Rather.
Is even after I deny. Getting
a word. Contract pregnant or seventy get
a blanket in the chest and you can stay
in the house or. CAPTAIN. I wonder
what you what next. What an episode at
Red House did not mean to the spring Mr
Morgan and I was in a scream in the
night above me others with a hill and
a human strong enough to nearly
kill me I figured it was you.
Sometimes we begin to rush out
around things. At every figured.
That is bad for everyone. It's quick
sand. And if you're having your
name. Right I want to hurt you.
But you don't happen to. Pursue what.
They know that.
I'm trying to stay with me. I shouldn't
matter what happened I packed them to me
got much too fast. After what happened
you couldn't get me out of here with
a triple barrel shotgun. I had I was
a coward. Some connection
between Pete Rouse never hit me
when I find out what goes on out there
protect the crime every Sunday between now
and Doomsday I have. A peep. Well not
to go on what I can't help but I want
to. Talk
a. Little crowd. Went
back into it with him because. I
want our kids back. And I don't
watch. I'm not. I don't
want to. Spoil your life
we did have a great Christmas
and Anyway maybe I can
a colossal keep going
another. Night. When I make.
It Up and down and I.
Don't practice dropping we've got
a home. Right
now and I've found maybe
I missed somewhere.
In the next.
Half.
An hour dead and. I'm hard.
Bad. With the past the station Perseid
our bank card house around. Town
night time now. Forgotten had
a day coterminous that. Just
occurred this. Remember.
The bank and the family just right when I.
Say. Until you. See
what's left. When I was
a black and blue streak across his shoulder
trying to get it all that. I don't know
caution. My flesh million
on your secret we have
a handle secret we tell you after
we had half lunch for the I.R.S.
I slept on
a screen last night from Marshall. And I
right across the pond Aren't you coming in
. Here at
a swimming day just the two of
you remember last time. Thank
.
You not many. Just keep the luckiest.
Man. On a planet of America
a bit. Like he's
a guest or like an honorary half or
sometimes I fall down. Flat happy at
our house today we missed having company
much come back often. Sides we like to
keep days happy. We had a pleasant day
where we wasted number seven looking for
a hot house to accept.
And I know that was a harder task
we are steroids. Well made. Says
a threat may backfire is
meant to like. Yesterday.
Whether.
There's enough to cover the much work
without having to grab another four in. The
hand of the family can
handle it they only knew it.
Well when you are keeping your secret
blabbing to Pete I didn't blab it just last
hour and
a fine one thing they had I don't think.
You're going to be you're mighty pretty
specially when you're mad. And I guess
maybe maybe when you're mad Yes that's
pretty scalars. Sure you don't want to get
people to come truck and drive you home
. Can't have your cake
and eat it to. Charge.
Come say. Those first I'll be saying
much every weeknight well and
final exam is coming up in this new job
I know. But if he too much at least the
next and he fires just to me or someone
part to play hide and seek in the works
with Meg. Get mad actually takes.
Don't think going to talk me into a kiss
goodbye. To the Mrs. Long enough to make
a month pregnant. Status makes.
Sure nappy. Dissipate me.
I understand it makes. Sense there's
no. He went into the race with
a nice rationale Ratchanok you know. We
can time the fans aren't in the kitchen
getting into one and after I don't care
now you listen to me. But I haven't
a word if you. Get anything you want I'll
get it for you but one thing you gotta do
for me. That I was just on a got
a right to do exactly I was never lay hands
on your My Life Project the people here
to.
Hide. From. But I figure
since women that you know.
That just are not baggage
is. Waiting for you.
But. I want you to do me
a favor. I've got lots
of recipe same size as
a here that kind of got more sense in your
head it comes out of your mouth. Maybe.
Kind of save you went out and.
Got seven hundred fifty bucks.
I want you to buy me
a government bond I have an address
you guys like you get your daily. I
want you to buy me that song I'm write my
name on and buy the next time you go to
town. There's an extra ten for your
travel so I can show you could.
Keep your mouth shut the boat. On the
waiting every senator you bring is fine and
should I just sell because I guy in
a village bank got too long
on notice. Because it'll be
a prettier bond if you buy
it for me. I don't get how.
Ramita how to cross
a drink. Thanks
so much. That all of thanks I
get. So much more you want.
Air.
Tell us. You're either protect these was
a minor I guess from an apparent alignment
you keep your trespassers on the gave me
for I see OG said what explosives I gave
you the game rights in exchange for giving
customers hours of Mr Morgan if you can
keep your own hired hand out of this but
maybe I should use more than
a crab to scam away with. So I don't
you're. Telling me I can use my gun I
don't want anybody to get hurt
but. No better way of backing up
a No Trespassing child and by
abolishing somebody's scout.
OK Mr Martin I'll take care my end. Is
going to be fine it's going to be my last
it's your last chance.
Any kind and when I came to Harvard
for getting money. Even if God Christ
has forgiven you. He
hadn't time. To pay to be.
This all those not listening. Not in his.
Camp in the bliss in the
pope in faith trying.
Money counseling you Pete you
haven't eaten the head of.
How. Yet to be are coming to the.
I want to have a. Now I'm
coming over I can use
a pickup truck maybe. They said I can
use this take up truck I come on down
by. Now and I was again mad
and in love Sunday was always
a good day for sporting. Thanks for the
use of the track. Always ready to give
love
a helping hand. I think
Maggie. Thatcher. And
I might add it's lot healthier
than prowling in words.
I don't care what I wish we were packed
with. Wish to be forgotten our date for the
last. Something else I was wanting.
Something tells me we won't find
out what it is until I finally asked. What
are we going to do with it when we find
. Busted open I guess much wine and.
Maybe I'll take the grapes out on
a fine. Frank.
I got this way
a graduation. I was going to give it
to you and to Lambert. Because it's
a great day and. Because
I want you to be happy.
Go ahead of me.
Like it or I love it. Let me put it down.
Little old new normal. Now
would you forgive me for
barking at your leisure on this. I
didn't expect you to suggest peace.
As are you trying to cling to those
words how did it become that I had to.
Change. Happen one day I.
Don't ever going to hear
those words you can't. Fathom.
Thanks for the one I
treasure down my life.
You. May.
Marry. A day
to remain
a loyal man with
a man and I thought
and I and I met. A man and I with.
A little bit of. A thousand I had in the.
Past and my. Man.
In man or another man I
am
a man. All right.
All right.
Greg thanks. Fred I
thought I.
Already late.
To say.
Thank.
The AS.
Friendly as.
Red. Rather.
Than
a. More enduring river. And
.
Heavy you've got Meg are going to ask
you after Sunday and have dinner have
a surprise. Can anybody do anything without
you figuring the gun angle I've always
gotten I've got an angle on you go it has
restarted just something special you're
OK and what's your reason for driving
with that guy Tyler what do you mean just
what I said and I got in so you.
Could you why were you. In the butt
more just like I was some
of that yes there was
a more darling I didn't know about
you don't think I'd be interested in
a big dumb ox to make his living hunting
you were interested enough to stop and
talk to him that afternoon while I was
sitting on our rocks I told him to get off
and what did he say he said.
I'll bet you calling me
a liar. I don't make something out of nothing
all I said was I'll bet you bet what
I'll bet he said he'd get off
your rock. And are calling you
a liar. Bob was right.
About was not too bright to be wasting your
time up the market to four bits an hour
I just live off their time to make
a profit on others. Some one of the longest
living off the earth. We're gonna live
off in a film day. Before we're
finished relieve our kids
a good farm. I want to clear out of these
hills when I get married. Some twenty
cents now I don't want to be just any
farm life. Is going to time and then the
other to find that out. In the field of
someone you'll do anything for.
That works both ways. Maybe some
day along this whole valley. And we can
spend our winters in the city have sure
been to station wagons
a limousine. Plan A. I'm
going to get back to the
more. Or less to go on with your dreaming
I'm disturbing your sleep city house
station wagons limousine great. Boy
when you dream you really dream good.
Well I was working for sure
a lot of guys are working on getting to
the moon in Iraq I think that's worth
working for but I like the ground around
here and I just assume keep my feet on it
how much money do you say doing it. None
Yeah not even seven hundred fifty dollars
. Seven hundred fifty
CENT Why not saying I was
just thanking.
They. May go with you I thought you did she
was gone when you left didn't she leave
with you this new not only for support
because she was going anywhere you must've
gone into the woods alone.
I mean you can. You are.
Yes Maybe Mom I'm stuck.
Here all this. Now but are you
always on the other like.
What happened here to lead by can. I
give up my trust me. Did everything I
asked. And then it came. To
singing. I fart
fade fifteen years ago.
You know that I love. Stay
away from that house it
is
a peach you tried. To call it.
I had to go to work. Don't
take it up again do you believe
Peste. Very aware boy came here
doesn't know anything about it Pete
that's only in your mind. You think is
a man on earth who hasn't something
to conceal. Every living soul has
a doctor that would actually still cheer.
You know there is nothing I could write
and he knew it don't pick it up again
do you please what is my goal before it
happened to the Irish Cream.
Man after she knew it.
Was which. Being to do is
he put it out of your mind
does it drive you mad again.
Gone over can touch me again.
There's nothing on there is something we
can do about it we can protect this in the
past and I protect it from
a passionate action at our pleasure we can
shout it out of this house now on now
this is my house. There's no certain
place beyond. Them out there and
I can't. Catch more
damage. That makes trying
to Pete Pete how could she find I didn't
want to go I'd rather she was dead than
ever hear the screams I rather she were
scared I'd rather I died out there in the
muck dirt actually. I should
have been that place down now.
That searched the ashers and find her
screaming pressure to bend it down in the
eyes half of the world where the truth.
Never dare tell an Open the door
Helen.
What's happened to us I found her in your
words her legs broken caught up to burn
her Jonathan teeth.
Where were the men and. Dr Burke.
Cockburn this people are going we
need you. Next legs broken Congress.
Name. Somebody out here.
I'm so glad to come home. But until the
last hour that may come and then about
climbing the tree into night I wanted to
tell you about that how. I talk to my
contractors of right and wrong grandmother
starts I don't know. How to help him
talk back to the last time
rock climbing. Asked him to.
Search me gone to town for something
graduation to think. Thank you.
Tell me about that house after the limestone
rock slide. My mommy cracks in the
rock go talk to father and I could pick
up the hill I don't know how it could be
a foreign tax to say. I'm
a farmer in the town going to the
rocks. Well Karen was. Quite.
Hungry. That night I had the
feeling I've been there before
a lot of people get that feeling
and I even if I haven't noticed
a difference. I even seem to remember
that back again for the hot.
Water Service Pack two hundred. Because
if it were flooded Taria know what an ice
mattress scares me I know it but how did I
put in the lock. I didn't dare because.
My heart started pounding. Train
a scream. I
think I did. I think that's
why I ran I don't know.
Better. Come on our. Air ticket.
When.
Things. Are you are right just turned up
my light. But I heard you calling me.
Now I was just back of.
Sleep soundly if you mean.
Your makes room just now. I was
picked up the tree. Was out on the
dock there are
a lot I guess missing or ask my. Space
in the house and tell you OK if you talk
around the water say going to the ones on
our own you would know God would want for
you or like would have been broken up at
once but you've got no I can't treat her
like
a child you caused all the trouble you're
going to. I don't want you here anymore.
Now you're going to think I want this job
I want to read and then today I like
Claire I. Have
a crisis on my property again if you do
you'll get hurt that's our running Yes
that's clear enough.
You can take my place off. Base credit
card worked every four weeks without even
saying goodbye. But it seems they made it
in this morning so to say goodbye to you
. It's not like Nate. Is
a nice boy. But it does do
to help. Rudy can manage to.
Make it will soon be of no around that
we can manage not. Just to name him to.
Make. You proud with one.
Headline to me Pete. I should I quarrel
with the Lord. The same reason you
kill Jeannie's husband. Because
you want to help yourself.
Make the. Days go. If you're his last.
He needed
a full time job now the
school about it that. I
was putting conditions
a random walk up it came down
amount. To mistake from three. It's
going to be too long for you isn't it. That
I'm just padlock the star and go up to
market Quest their mom. Went to work for
the rest. Going to be around and you
won't be long. I'll be OK Mom.
Well happy honey mom. Thanks
again for everything.
Good bye. Bye.
Good bye darling good bye mom.
I was not patient but it feels better
that cast off I've been taking
a back injury time knocking
that may take. About
a female. Whereas I want gathering.
Up everyone in the valley below new baby
a chair poked your right hand at the wrist
and kind of. Like the storm's going mate
. Everybody's wondering what the rest
is what I'm supposed to stand by for
a son in law right next door and on the
farm for free as most living up to the full
steam going back to the store nice day was
he working at the time you're broke is
pretty nice. Yes but he had to
get a full time job he's got
a full time job and he could be
he's a radical. Well. I've got
a few babies coming here old folks
dying I gotta be going I have
a lot of after. Meg's about as good
as new young bones and. Fast but if I
haven't you would like a lot of
what I said yes but then I've got
a meager forty like more than
a man does. It really help being careful
he can forget the grudges and I'll swear
I'll take care of that. I watch or
like the same Bernard. That went.
All right. Said our former.
High.
Remember when I had to learn to
walk again. Just like climbing
a mountain all day long. That I
lean on me. Nice and dry to my
first. I just want to help
you. That's what I thought.
That's what I like.
High. What you got on
my new places to write
sorry. You guys will still be working with
the mortgage crowd the fun you are to me
if you spend
a little more time working around the place
and set up preening your feathers like
a canary maybe you know what
it is to be tired and I had
a nice Sunday picnic I planned for some
odd on my strength that's not going to
waste it on you face all day if you want
to. Just go ten or eleven. Didn't play
twenty ten or eleven up at the margins
because you wanted to see her. Do it stick
your head under a faucet the cool off T.V.
You want to go on that
picnic tomorrow I'll be at
a level. The
.
It's. A.
Fine of up to my other class.
Based upon I've been here every Sunday but
I couldn't get here before today what do
you think you are standing me up you've
been drinking so what contact payment on
time I got your old son to
tell anybody you are drunk.
Who are you kidding you can
put around a pretty born
a storm as much as you like
but when you decide on
a man you come to me. Tell
him I'm
a. Dad to catch you when it was crunch tried
on time when he fell but just want you
can you.
Can just say you not want to me. Yeah I can
next time you feel like snooping around
on Ted would. Read the sign the part
about at your own risk why because
some yellow belly are
stuck me in the dark.
Because I got bored right to them what OK
I'm twenty eight Morgan. And would you be
knowing how Meg broke her
leg. Oh I'd. Better be
your snooping around each one to
get this. To happen. And I tell
you let's get out of here.
This is the way football
is this bitch. We don't
need any play.
But from that which. I don't know I
think again. You miss me it's going
to. Be. Something from
here I don't know plenty.
God I'm going to break.
Down. Some ways to.
Read you hear that name economy that several
times and when he does I'm afraid when
he called you that name up in my room when
I read with her not by the time. He did
laid hands on you. By the way that.
Contradicted the.
Moving around. You know.
You're working too
hard to eat why don't you get naked back
to health. You're better off without it
I'm sure I'll make Mrs King she's
young she deserves the company of
a nice boy like my little son. That's what
you said about half an hour years ago.
Perhaps now it was fun for them but I
didn't have time to learn out of hand I was
too busy earning the money that would make
it possible to me to ask Cheney to be my
wife. Perhaps now especially becoming the
best dancer in the battery makes like you
not that he's a timetable
on this the hard work. Has
a girl what does he want with Meg Meg needs
to be with young people like me you can
condemn her to loneliness. Make the lawn
chair with ash you want to change out of
this place all her life my life yes I've
given my life to you Peter because you're
my brother and I love you you need me you
know what it meant to me but I've lost.
You know what Jonathan Vernon I might have
had all that I ask you not to marry him
no but you would let me take make with me
if I did the Jewish back me to whatever
happiness I get I've got to find what I
live you can find happiness by giving it
what you think I got I know what I buy
back here if you think you stop running on
those words until he found the red house
if you will stop at that he dictates for
you dig up a scum and bring it home as
a trophy. What do you think that would do
to make what you think would happen to if
you found out the truth if you loved me
all the rest of my life but you've got to
be said to make All right so I'm not
fair but I can't let it go. As long as
a red hot star from my sorry hole
like this makes my life it's mine.
What are you going to do with I'm going
to burn that place of the peace of mind I
don't care to talk to put up by going up
in flames tonight you can't go under the
bridge I know them well enough it isn't
that I didn't tell you or NATO troops about
how my legs broken I fell but it was because
somebody was shooting at me I'm afraid
make a good shot of pray tell
a. Peaceful to let him tell
a thing he owns those words just trying
to scare you but he's afraid of me let me
go with you know your legs I'm strong enough
I don't want to stay here alone I was
these thousand icecap and luck of the sea
and I'll be back before Pete knows I'm
gone. A little.
Well. Where. It's. A.
Break here.
The next. Morning.
Thank you. Right thank
you my friend I got.
It Done. That. I didn't
even kill the teleplay.
Damage.
The brain injury which our.
Colleagues lost. Last.
Night it was. If you're not going to say
you're not exactly is going to the Red
House. Fifteen years those
which have been coming
out of style. Now
it can't go nobody can. Know what.
Person on the train we can just performers
go on so mock. A conductor burning the
share price pressure area is. Not
going back and then you can't do it
for the last you believe me I know what the
results and I know what's there I know
the dangers. Don't expect God. You don't
become.
Company. You'll be fine.
You'll get everything
you. Can. Always count on.
Me to. The security slips now. And lead.
You.
To. It eight.
Hours to sleep advantage to Uncle Sam.
I made a stretcher out of a blanket
a couple of breaks so all I had to do.
That compared to what and then I left
a message
a comma Cheryl. Leaving
off the sound. She's
dead.
Like you don't you mind me.
I can get you out of my mind.
That's the way I was made to.
Mr something about this bar your father's
truck and I don't. Love Holy Smoke I
think still come on baby. Drive
across the state are cash in my bond.
Sponges having
a honeymoon time and the honeymoon anybody
ever. Checks in the orchard shed we can
head out the back road they want here.
She says and.
You think I didn't love em.
Every day for years died from
a. Good thing I can forget that.
But you forgot the words. That's
what's kept. You hate me now
don't you. Think. You let out that.
You decide to work in your. Shit asylum.
And then again maybe. He
always understood. You maybe
that I spoke about you. Everything I'm
not.
Anti Bush or Cheney coming
to. The Lodge so I was
a real name and out of the question the
past I don't know I don't know I don't stay
here and. Yet. You wash your mouth.
Now you have it bad happened I make for the
love of heaven if you want to know one
thing but it was an action and I have been
an accident coming on how much to have
you want to pay it every day to have.
Worship your. No man ever loved the world
whether it was your marriage your product
a man without heart without sorrow that you
carry around or you're going to believe
me may. I never hurt you.
And every so much that
a harsh word to us. And then when you
abandon the red house I loved you like you
were my. Back slapping. Response. He got
challenged. Because to accusing G.-D.
And me of. That famous. Liar.
But the West Was Won and even taking
a new way. Around to the Red House to bring
with him or not to go ahead and come
home and are sorry I begged her to recite
the fortress too late. She got frightened
. In
a rash. Creams. No reason I
was interested he didn't
kill another with an axe and I just tried
to keep it quiet I just put my hand over
money that. The U.S.
Patent. And he came in
a little room. With my wrist. And
I knew it was serious too or he
was the one who was killed.
Because I'm literally.
Estimating already written. An atom and I.
Have become the body and then when I'm in
the center of what the past is and I am
sure it was pretty broken so many.
Mistakes. And I came to my senses and
tried to kill myself I jumped in the back.
Now should have already died there.
Let it Ride the why. Not me.
And I'm like you the Mini Me. I don't know
the words and I know you can't you've
got to tell me nothing don't forget one
of the notable reading is you can make it
to one hundred nineteen over again if
you're going to. Recommend this to. Be
free. From the red Hobson
You're going to stop the
car catch up with you.
Might have to found out was that all
that was twenty minutes. After maybe.
The fact that fact that out of the van.
The AS.
A fast pass. I didn't know what I'm
doing every time I didn't need to
get but it all adds up to
murder. Murder. Theft.
F F F F F F F
F F
F F. F.
I'm.
Right now I came as quickly as I could.
A couple of state highway players.
Any time to tell and no show
but I don't hire one so the.
Ins.
I'll be afraid.
To come out of the chorus is.
I'm left with are.
Things changed.
Just like your genes. I've come to plead
with you not to go don't go with them gee
I can't live without
you. I think we can have
a little you can be care. I care
thank you. It's hard not to like
much and I would kill for you and.
It goes back to the village I got the
baby was going to. Shrink wrapped
around it take away your stranger
with your. Misplaced I'm.
Just trying to distract.
Read. A message to
read.
Read read. Mad Men.
Men read the number change read.
Read. Make. A
decision. Then read it as.
A matter of regret. L.
L L.
S N L read. It i.
Read it and then rent.
Air. Read and
a red red red red
red red. Red.
Thank.
You. I'm not going to finish
well I'm fed up because we are
I just part of the Red House. Looking
forward much Bob Franken has been. An al.
Gore an air. Burst
their first airing left their.
Eggs entering well.
THANK YOU THANK YOU
THANK YOU.
Thank Ed.